# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

I am a hardworking, motivated, and ambitious individual with outstanding technical skills. I am passionate to begin a career in IT and so undertook a study programme to prepare me for the IT sector, with exposure to Cloud Computing. I recently graduated from a Cloud Engineer Programme specialising in troubleshooting hardware and software issues through a series of courses, practical work, and official certifications. I have a commitment to high standards when dealing with customers and staff members and possess excellent communication skills at all levels. I am confident that I will hit the ground running and be an asset to your organisation.

## **PERSONAL DETAILS**

NAME: Tomasz Dudek

**RESIDES**: Doncaster | UK

**CONTACT DETAILS:** (M) +44 (0) 7784003686

(E) tdudek62@gmail.com

### **CLOUD ENGINEER PROGRAMME**

### **IT Certify Ltd**

Cloud Engineer Programme July 2022 – February 2024

The Cloud Engineer Programme focused on preparing me for the IT Support sector with exposure to Cloud Computing through a series of intense courses and practical application.

Courses studied included:

CompTIA IT Fundamentals, CompTIA A+, CompTIA Network+, CompTIA Cloud+, ITIL Foundation, MCSA Microsoft Windows 10, CompTIA Linux+, Cloud Computing Security Knowledge, Microsoft Azure and Amazon Web Services.

- Installing, Configuring & migrating Windows 10 Operating Systems
- Configuring Security systems & Windows firewall
- Troubleshooting common system and cloud problems
- Configuring and managing printers, configuring mobile devices
- Configure, manage, and maintain essential network devices
- Design and implementing a functional network
- Active Directory unlocking user accounts, resetting passwords, searching users
- Implement network security, standards, and protocols

I have recently passed my CompTIA A+ qualifications specialising in troubleshooting hardware and software issues. More information on this certification can be found at: <a href="https://certification.comptia.org/certifications/a">https://certification.comptia.org/certifications/a</a>

# 2023: CompTIA A+ 220-1101 & 1102 Certification

### **SYSTEMS EXPERIENCE:**

Windows desktop systems, install, patching, troubleshooting, hardware replacement

Extensive experience with the Microsoft Office suite

Thorough understanding of computer, networking and security concepts Working knowledge of Windows 10, Active Directory, PowerShell, Remote Access/Desktop and VMware.

Knowledge of many programming languages including C, C++, Python, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, jQuery, and . NET.

### **CAREER HISTORY:**

# January 2022 to January 2024 POSITION HELD:

### Multi skilled Electrician at Aggreko Limited

- Conducted electrical assembly, wiring, and support for manufacturing products following quality control protocols.
- Assembled, wired, and inspected control panels for DC and 3-phase AC systems, including LV, HV, and MV systems.
- Proficient in precision tool use, including air tools, hand tools, torque tools, and measuring equipment.
- Certified forklift driver (Bendi) for safe and efficient material handling.
- Diagnosed and repaired distribution boards, performed RCD tests, executed cable and socket replacements, and replaced circuit breakers for optimal electrical distribution.

# January 2021 to January 2022 POSITION HELD:

# Machine Operator/ Production Administrator at Wren Kitchen, Howden

- Operated a variety of woodworking machinery including CNC drills, adhering to detailed technical drawings to produce high-quality products.
- Booked stock into IFS for goods in and goods out, coordinated supportive admin tasks, and solved problems as needed.

# January 2016 to January 2021 POSITION HELD:

### **Logistics Coordinator and Vehicle Driver**

- Drove throughout the UK collecting and delivering vehicles and goods for various companies, including BCA Automotive Logistics, MIS Conversions Doncaster, and Amazon.
- Delivered and inspected cars and vans throughout the UK while providing a high level of customer service.
- Demonstrated good topographic knowledge of the UK and planning skills to support business and private clients.

# January 2014 to January 2016 POSITION HELD:

## **CNC Machine Operator at Kaby Engineers Ltd**

- Operated a range of machines, including grinding, hardening saw machines, and milling machines, using technical drawings, and measuring devices to ensure end products of the highest standard.
- Provided support to the paint shop and worked for dispatch.

#### **EDUCATION**:

2022 – 2024: IT Certify | London, UK Cloud Engineer Programme

2008 - 2013: Technical University in Rzeszow, Poland

Bachelor's degree in industrial Commodity Science in Engineering - Level 6

### **OTHER CERTIFICATIONS:**

CompTIA A+ Core 1
CompTIA A+ Core 2
CompTIA A+ Core 2 Practice Lab
CompTIA Cloud+ Practice Lab